Remember that project we talked about?
还记得那个项目 我们谈过的吗?
Welcome to the United States of America.
欢迎来到美国.
When you arrive,
当你到达时,
follow the "Arrivals" sign.
跟着"抵达"标志走.
First you have to go through Immigration and Passport Control.
首先你必须通过入境处和护照检查处.
Make sure you have the correct visa,
确保你有正确的签证,
if needed,before you arrive.
如果需要的话, 在你到达前.
And then it's time to get your bags.
然后到了拿你行李的时候了,
Follow signs to the Baggage Claim.
跟着标志去行李认领处.
TV monitors will tell you exactly where your luggage will arrive.
电视屏幕会确切地告诉你 你的行李会到达哪里.
After you get your baggage,
你拿到你的行李后.
go through customs.
通过海关.
If you have something to declare,
如果你有什么东西要申报.
go through the red exit.
通过红色的通道.
If not,go through the green exit.
如果没有, 通过绿色通道.
We hope you enjoy your stay in the United States.
我们希望你享受你在美国的停留.
Have a nice day.
祝你有美好的一天.
You did this on the computer?
你弄了这个  在电脑上?
You're just a big genius!
你真是个了不起的天才!